Abdul Haseeb

54 Poddle Close, Kimmage, Dublin 12

Mob.: 086 322 5963

Email: ahaseeb235@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 05 Feb 1980 Nationality: Indian

Born and raised in Saudi Arabia, I am an Indian national living in Ireland for the past 15 years, with fluency in English, Arabic, Urdu and Hindi languages, both spoken and written. With a strong focus on client needs, customer service and quick to learn and adapt, I am an enthusiastic, open-minded and flexible person; I have a keen understanding of cultural nuances so I enjoy a diverse working environment and I am always look for opportunities to learn and develop my skills.

Work Experience

Sep 2014 to Date Reads Print and Design, Sandyford Office Park, Sandyford,

Dublin 18

Job title: Printer/Designer

Main responsibilities include customer service, advice and plan print processes and printing, finishing, design and layout. I regularly deal with clients from the Middle East and North Africa, and with Irish clients who provide products and services to the Middle East and North African markets.

Jan 2013 - Aug 2014 Dublin Welfare Society, 3 Station Street, Dublin 1

Job title: Projects Coordinator

Main responsibilities included coordination of the development

of the Clongriffin Mosque Project.

Other responsibilities include the coordination between the

various projects run by the Dublin Welfare Society.

Jan 2009 - Dec 2012 Irish Muslim Magazine, 17 Synge Street, Dublin 8

Job Title: Editor/Publisher

Responsibilities included design, edit and publication of the monthly magazine, dealing with a variety of clients from

Middle East and Asia.

Jul 2006 - Dec 2008 Near90fm Radio, Coolock Civic Centre, Coolock, Dublin 13

Job Title: Presenter/Producer

Part time job included producing and presenting 30 minute radio programme (Islam in Focus) on a weekly basis in addition to producing/editing short documentaries and/or interviews for the

radio station.

Apr 2005 - Mar 2006 Islamic Foundation of Ireland, 163 South Circular Road, Dublin 8

Job Title: Administrator

Job included administrative work, community liaison and development, translations, events and projects management.

Jul 2004 - Mar 2005 Rathmines Call@Net, Rathmines Road, Dublin 8

Job Title: Technical Support/Network Administrator

Responsibilities included providing tech support, Network and

Systems administration and customer service.

Apr 2001 - June 2004 Four Seasons Hotel, Ballsbridge, Dublin 4

Job Title: F&B Server

Responsibilities included Guest food and beverage service

Education

November 2016 IASSC Certified Green Belt

May 2004 Diploma in Hotel and Catering Management

Dublin Institute of Technology, Cathal Burgha Street, Dublin 1

1999 - 2001 Year 1 & 2, BA in Hospitality Management

Thames Valley University - RMI DELHI campus

New Delhi, India

Language Skills

English, Arabic, Urdu and Hindi (spoken and written)

Computer Skills

- Proficient in MS Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, inDesign.
- Medium level skills in HTML5, CSS, Javascript and Bootstrap.
- Medium level skills in Joomla CMS.

References

References can be provided upon request.